传媒大亨洛根·罗伊在哪里
爸
-汤姆 她去哪儿了  -正在中转或是在隧道里吧
- Tom, where is she, huh? - She must be in transit or a tunnel.
罗曼的电话
Roman.
-小西去哪儿了  -我不知道啊 老爸
- Where's Shiv? - "I don't know where she is, Dad."
到底他妈的咋回事儿 大家是什么态度
What the fuck's going on? What's everyone saying?
我要知道所有人的位置和想法
I need to know where everyone is and what everyone's thinking.
你在哪儿呢
"Where are you?"
可能要去拉个粑粑 刮个胡子 再洗个澡吧
You know, heading for a shit, shave, and a shower.
不行 我要康纳稳住阵脚
"No. No. I need Connor steadied."
我需要玛西娅 小西和赛德 还有他妈的...
I need Marcia. I need Shiv. I need Ray and Cyd and fucking...
儿子 你也得过来露脸
I need you showing your face for me, son.
你想让我跟肯谈谈吗
You want me to go talk to him, to Ken?
不想 去他妈的 谁都不许跟这个卑鄙的人说话
"No! Fuck that. No. No one talks to the snake, no."
跟紧格丽 行吗
Keep Gerri close. Hmm?
盯着点儿她 我很信任你的
Keep an eye on, huh? I trust you.
但我们非格丽不可 今时今日只得这样
"It just had to be Gerri. For right now. For today. "
好吧 我懂了 老爸
Uh, yeah. Uh, yeah. I get it, Dad.
继   承   之   战
第 3 季  第 2 集
格雷格 咱们来钻空子 给你外公打电话
Okay, Greg. Let's game a call with your Grandpa.
让尤恩做好战斗的准备
I'd like us to get Ewan squared off.
-好的 我觉得...  -能行吗
- Oh, yeah. Yeah. I think... - Yeah?
我觉得... 是不是 应该你来打啊 对吧
I guess... Maybe you ought to just do that, right?
-伙计 你还好吧  -还好
- You okay, dude? - Yeah.
你是不是觉得自己上了贼船了[把牛子绑在火车上]
You wondering if you tied your dick to a runaway train here?
什么玩意儿 不不不 我是说...
What? No, no, no. I mean...
-你该不是个叛徒吧 格雷格  -不是
- You aren't Judasing are you, Greg? - No. No.
来 老兄 咱俩交流交流感情
Come here. Come on, buddy. Come here. Let's huddle.
-怎么了  -这个嘛
- What's up? - Yeah.
-我说不清 我...  -来跟我说说
- I don't know. I'm... - Talk to me.
我...
I...
我不知道该怎么说 就是有点儿害怕
I don't know. I am, uh, just a bit scared.
我不想...
Like, I don't...
你懂的 我不想再面对国会了
You know, I don't really wanna go to Congress again.
我还太年轻了 不适合总去国会 能理解吧
I'm kind of too young to be in Congress so much, you know?
我爸联系你了吗
Did my dad get to you?
汤姆一直在联系我
Tom keeps calling.
他就是想知道
He just wants to know
我们哪儿来的文件... 不对 是你哪儿来的...
where we got the papers and... or you got...
-听着...  -并且文件里写了什么
- Look... - And what's in the papers, and...
小伙子 我没有准备牺牲你
I'm not gonna burn you, kiddo.
文件哪儿来的我连政府都不会告诉
I don't even have to tell the government where I got the papers.
-好吧 你说过你不会说的  -对啊
- Well, you said you wouldn't tell them. - Yeah.
-我是有原则的  -好的
- And... and I'll stick by that. - Yeah.
-肯  -所以别...
- Hey, Ken. - So, don't... Yeah.
-雷米来了  -最近怎么样
- Remi's here. - Hey. What up?
-雷米大驾光临  -兄弟还好吗
- Remi in the house. - What's up, bro?
大事儿 大事儿
Big things. Big things.
老兄 你做了正确的事
You did the right thing, man.
我也想做正确的事
I want to do the right thing.
好吧 我们来缓解你的不适
Okay. Let's settle your stomach.
我们... 我们给你找个律师吧 好不
Let's... let's set you up with a lawyer, okay?
-肯  -好吧
-Ken. - Okay.
-肯  -什么事
- Ken? - Yeah?
赞啊 挺好
Oh, fuck yeah. Okay.
你... 你能处理一下这里吗
Can... can you figure this out?
大家好 抱歉打断一下
Uh, hi, everyone. Sorry to interrupt.
我们... 得借用这间房一小会
If... We... we just need the room for a little bit.
所以... 得五分钟十分钟的
So, um... Take a five, take a ten...
谢谢 谢谢各位大佬
Thank you. Thank you, mental giants.
借过一下... 我想上一下电梯... 谢谢
Can I... I'm gonna hop in that elevator while it's still... Thank you.
真漂亮
Very nice.
喂
Hello?
你好啊 格雷戈里
"Hello, Gregory."
汤姆 这不是汤姆的电话啊
Tom? Th... this... this isn't the Tom number.
我知道 我是不是很聪明啊
I know. Aren't I clever?
格雷戈里 你有惊天秘密 对吧
Hey, Gregory, is it true you have a saucy secret?
我... 我还真不知道你在讲什么... 你是...
I... I actually don't know what you're talking... Are you...
你喜欢光着屁股做家务吗
Do you like to do your house chores in the nude?
喂 什么
"Hello? What?"
到底他妈的咋回事儿 格雷格
What the fuck is going on, Greg?
我不知道 兄弟 我只是个旁观者
I don't know, man. I'm just an observer.
我跟这件事没多大关系
I'm not a part of this necessarily.
罗根对你正在搞的小九九很感兴趣
"Well, Logan is very interested what you're up to."
你不回我们这儿来的话 就等着去集中营吧
You don't come home to us, you're gonna end up in a work camp.
罗根要在你的裤裆里放成千上万只毒蜘蛛
Logan is going to fire a million poisonous spiders down your dicky.
你最好找一具动物尸体爬进去藏起来吧
You better find an animal's corpse to crawl into and hide.
我... 真的跟这事没关系 汤姆
I... I'm not a part of this, necessarily, Tom.
好吧 那你怎么解释那些文件
Okay. What about the papers?
我不... 我可能不知道它们是什么 也不知道是哪儿来的
I don't... I maybe don't even know what they are or where they came from.
算了 行 那我们要看看他信不信你的鬼话了
Fine. Okay. Well, we'll have to see if he buys that.
我是说... 我能告诉你...
Well... I... I mean, I can say...
你知道小西在这里吗
Did you know that Shiv's over there?
慢着 在肯德尔那儿吗
Wait. At Kendall's?
对 你知道吗
"Yeah. Di... Did you know?"
当然了 但是...
Yeah. Obviously. But...
我们先暂时咽在肚子里好吗[掩在牛仔帽下] 小牛仔
let's just keep that under the old Stetson for now, okay, cowboy?
好的 长官 遵命
Yeah. Yes, sir. Yessiree.
-小西有消息了吗  -什么
- Any Shiv news? - Um, what?
-小西  -小西吗 还没有
- Shiv. - Shiv? Uh, no, no, no.
现在还没有消息
Not as yet. Nothing.
没有好消息
No... no luck there.
-好了  -好啦
- Okay. - Okay?
对 我给斯图伊打了电话 然后他送来了这个
Yeah. Oh, and I called Stewy and asked, and this came from him.
它...
It's, um...
-好吧 这算个笑话吗  -它...
- Okay. Is that a joke? - It's...
那谁... 谁是特洛伊木马
Who... who's the Trojan horse here?
你想... 你想看看里面吗
You want... you want me to look inside of it?
这是心理游戏 把它送回去
It's mind games. Send it back.
安排一下 我要见他
And set something, I need to see him.
没问题吧
We good?
是的 没问题
Yeah. We're good.
他在这儿啊 这个挑起大战的小人
There he is, the little man who started this big war.
你还好吗
How you doing?
我们能私下谈谈吗
Can we get out of the sunlight please?
谁卖了你一匹汗血宝马
Who sold you the Thoroughbred?
安时公司得到了投资公司格拉尼特控股集团的支持
"Safetime is backed by investment firm Granite Holdings Incorporated"
该公司去年一整年
"Who stood by Safetime
都在援助安时公司的技术问题
throughout last year's technological issues."
-现在在安时公司...  -我的天哪
- "Now at Safetime's..." - Oh, my God.
瞧瞧你 在拍你小小的名字
Look at you photograph your tiny name.
给我女儿拍的
Well, you know, for my daughters.
好吧 太有爱了
Oh, right. That is so cute.
你女儿什么样 有照片吗
How are your daughters? You got pictures?
别谈论我女儿
Don't talk about my daughters.
瞧瞧 让我知道了你的软肋
Look at you, telling me the sensitive areas.
你了解我的 我会毕恭毕敬的
You know me, I'll be respectful.
所以真就这样吗 这一切真的发生了
So this is it, huh? It's actually happening.
福无双至 祸不单行
The odor prevails. The gas also rises.
你懂的 就像
Well, you know, it's like
当你看到教皇和帝王的名单
when you see those lists of popes and emperors,
有些名字还加了星号
and some of them have asterisks by their names.
所以 有好多事情我想跟你说
So, couple of things I wanted to talk to you about.
我就是想确认...
I just wanna make sure...
来确认你没有太担心那些乱七八糟的事
Check that you're not concerned about all of this stuff.
我完全不知道你说的是什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我希望你别焦虑到...
I hope that you're not anxious that you've, you know,
把自己栓到消防栓上
chained yourself to a fire hydrant
被这个消防栓喷射的文化麻木和精液淹没
that spews out cultural insensitivity and sperms.
听着 罗曼 我不会在任何事上自欺欺人
Look, Roman, I'm not kidding myself about anything.
我需要家里人支持
I need family support,
所以我乐于接受合作 听取建议
so I'm very open to cooperation and input.
-对  -你直觉很好
- Right. - And you have good instincts.
-谢谢你  -但也有不好的时候
- Thank you. - You also have horrible instincts,
比如 不合作这个点子就是灾难
like the... not cooperating is a disaster.
但是呢 你也有很好的洞察力 洞察...
But you also have a good finger on the pulse of, uh... in terms of...
你是说我有时会网上冲浪吗
You mean I sometimes surf the web?
对 你懂的 新闻和文化之类的
Yeah. You know, news and culture, and whatnot.
你... 你有直觉...
You're... you have an instinctive...
谢谢 我有思想的
Thank you. I have a thought.
我觉得你应该召集执行委员会
I think you should put together an executive committee
来领导这一段空白期
to guide things in this interregnum.
好吧 你知道我不太想分权
Well, you know, I don't wanna dilute my potency.
是 但是宏观来说 你让大家的手上都沾上了血
Yeah. But on the big calls, you dip everyone's hands in blood.
但是你和我 我们才能一起经营
But you and me, we run it to fuck.
听着 我在想我们的第一步应该是
See, I was thinking that first we'd start with, you know,
让你控股四分之一 这是一个信号
working you into the quarterly earnings calls as a signal.
-但是 你知道...  -很好 会是个好的开始
- But, uh, you know... - Likey-likey. That's a good start.
我再想想执行委员会的事儿 毕竟...
Let me think about the executive committee thing. I mean...
-好  -...切入角度很好
- Yeah. - ...it has good angles.
就像他无可替代一样
You know, like he's irreplaceable.
我们六个人才能替代他一个人
It takes six of us to replace one of him.
那就这样吧 你的学徒生涯开始了
Here we go. Your apprenticeship begins.
好啊
Okay.
-好  -那好
- Yeah. - Okay.
那么 小西西 别来无恙啊
So, Shivy, how we doing?
瞧瞧你 脸都笑烂了 丽莎在吗
Look at you, all fucking merry. Is Lisa here?
我有一项提议
I have an offer.
是吗 可我不是为此而来的
Yeah, that's not why I'm here.
放心 我不是在开玩笑
Well, I'm not gonna fuck around.
我要你加入我
I want you to join me.
我要你跟我站在同一条战线上
I want you on my side.
我不是来和你套近乎的
I'm not here to cozy up.
的确
No.
但我还是想说 爸对你做的一切...
But I would say, what dad did to you...
和你因此所付出的 的确有点过了
the sacrifice, that was cold.
我也不确定 但在他看来 这么做的确不为过
Well, I don't know. From his point of view, it made sense.
要不然 他还能怎么办
I mean, who else was he gonna choose?
除非 你也懂的 除非他自己承担所有的责任
Unless, you know, he took responsibility himself.
-说得没错  -所以...
- Well, yeah. - So...
所以什么 我知道你很生气
So? I get it. You were angry.
他之前那么做确实太狠毒了
That was a fucking snake move.
好了 我知道 我只是...
Yeah. I... I know. I just...
听着 过去的事就让它过去吧
Look, the situation was the situation.
当时我也别无选择
I felt I had no choice.
得了吧 肯 别来自卖自夸这一套
Come on, Ken. That was self- aggrandizing bullshit.
简直和孔雀台放的节目一样蠢
It was a peacock fuck-show.
我理解你 妹妹
That's fair. I get it, sis.
我知道你对自己很懊恼
You're angry with yourself.
抱歉 说什么鬼呢
I'm sorry. What?
你知道我做了对的事
You know I did the right thing
你很懊恼没能像我一样这么做
and you're angry with yourself for never doing it.
-拜托 去你的吧  -这正是...
- Come on. Fuck you. - That's just...
一切正如我刚刚所说的
what I would say is going on here.
-如果你不这么想的话  -根本不是这样
- But if you don't see it that way... - That is not it.
-是吗  -你干翻了整个家族
- Sure. - You fucked the family.
亦或是我挽救了整个家族
Or I saved the family?
我觉得自从出了这些乱子后
I think since this thing broke,
大家一直都在这种互相内斗的...
we've all been trying to navigate our way through...
两难处境中徘徊 这很难
conflicting loyalties, and that's difficult.
你骗自己是个好人
You tell yourself you're a good person.
可实际上你不是
But you're not a good person.
现在 我才是你内心最真实的想法
Right now, I'm the real you.
什么
What?
可不是嘛 你是我内心最真实的想法
Sure. You're the real me.
你思即我想
And I'm the real you.
行了吗 随你吧
Yeah? What-fucking-ever.
她到底在哪
Where is she
等等 我看看...
Yeah. Hold up. Let's see...
你联系过玛西娅吗 有谁在联系吗
Have you spoken to Marcia? Is someone connecting?
我们听说她有空 需要联系她吗
She's available, we hear. You wanna reach out?
我他妈当然想联系她 雨果
Yes, I wanna fucking reach out, Hugo.
我现在被困在流沙里
I'm stuck in quicksand.
而我的家人集体失踪 整个世界都在摇摇欲坠
My family have disappeared. The world is wobbling here.
他妈的就没人意识到事情的严重性吗
Does no one understand what the fuck is happening?
我在大出血 而且还他妈找不到一个合适的律师
I'm losing juice. I can't find the right fucking lawyer.
天都要塌下来了
The sky is falling in.
所以我下次吩咐什么 都他妈给我落实了
So when I say something, it fucking happens.
我们得行动起来
We have to act on the world.
先发制人 得动起来
The fucking world. We have to act.
明白了
Yes, sir.
给她打过去 还有康 我的兄弟
Get her up. Con, my brother.
好好地给我出谋划策
And get me some options,
要是可靠的计策 最好能飞过去
some solid fucking options where we can fly.
我可不想到时候被塞进行李箱
I'm not gonna smuggle out
偷偷地运出去 听到了吗
of here in a fucking packing case, okay?
-联系上她了没  -还在...
- You got her? - Still...
康纳
Connor.
-康吗  -在 在
- Con? - "Hey. Hey."
-你那边怎么样  -我挺好的
- How you doing? - "I'm great."
我们已经按时抵达了 所以还蛮让人欣慰的
We flew back scheduled, so that was just delightful.
非常抱歉 儿子 辛苦你了
I'm sorry, son. That's tough.
还好啦
It was fine.
那边有各种各样的电影和冰冻奶酪芝士
They had movies and a selection of heavily refrigerated cheeses,
所以说 事实上还不错
so, you know, it was really nice.
总而言之 我就是想…
You know, I just wanted to say
跟你打个招呼 还有 很感谢你在那边做的一切
hello and, you know, thanks for holding the fort.
应该的 守株待兔行动嘛 正如你所说的
Sure. Operation: Thumb-Twiddle. You bet.
现在我们有空聊聊了
And now that we got a moment,
我之前在船上说的那些
those words, maybe harsh
可能有点难听的话...
words on that tin can on the boat, you know...
无伤大雅吧
Yes. So no harm done?
你真的太鲁莽了 爸
You're pretty rude, Pop.
我... 我只想让你知道 在发生了这么多后...
I... I'd just like to say, it's good to know that...
在小肯发疯后 还能继续信赖你
with everything, I can rely on you,
真的太好了
with Kenny going nut-nut.
当然 没问题 当然了
Yeah. Sure. You know... Yeah.
目前还没人和他谈过吧
Now, no one speaks to him, right?
你一直是我心中的第一名 小子
You're number one, kiddo.
你明白的
You know that.
第一名
Number one.
所以这些声名远扬的文件在哪
So where are these famous papers?
安全的地方 正在复印
Safe. Getting copied.
没有这些文件的话 一切都一笔勾销了
You know, lose those, all this goes away.
烧了吧 好好和爸道歉 去求他原谅
Burn them. Go say sorry to dad. Beg for mercy.
也就是说我吃寿司吃坏了肚子...
Right. Say I had some deli sushi...
所以做了这些傻事
and everything went a little hazy.
-小西 别闹了  -好主意
- Shiv, come on. - Great idea.
我已经下定决心了 而且我希望你加入我这边
No. I'm doing this, and I want you on my side.
-那就给我看看文件  -这可不行
- So show me the papers. - Well, I can't.
除非你确定站在我这条线上
Unless you wanna come on board with me.
但你也知道 我必须得...
But, you know, I gotta...
肯德尔 你有客人
Kendall, you have a visitor?
罗曼在楼下 那敢情好啊
Roman's downstairs. Okay.
-有点意思  -需要请他上来吗
- Now we're talking. - Shall I send him up?
-他知道有谁在这吗  -他知道她在这吗
- Well, does he know who's here? - Does he know she's here?
我... 我没和他说
I... I didn't mention it.
你想让他上来吗
You wanna let him up?
-我觉得...  -你才是我最想要的 小西
- I mean... - You're the one I want, Shiv.
我最想你加入
I want you.
那好 叫他上来吧
Sure. We should bring him in.
那好 杰西
Okay. Jess.
-好的  -带他上来
- Okay. - Show him up.
丽莎需要你两分钟时间
Lisa needs two minutes.
格雷格 这地方真的太棒了
Greg, this place is amazing.
过奖了 但是 这房子不是我的
Thank you. Yeah. It's, not mine.
总而言之 非常感谢你的夸奖
It's... Anyway, I'm very grateful.
是这样的
So,
肯德尔想给我请一个律师
Kendall wants to pay for my lawyer.
但我觉得... 你...
And I just... Well, do you...
你先说 从法律的角度上你怎么看
You say. What... what do you think, legally?
我连第一个学期都没上完呢 格雷格
I haven't even finished first semester, Greg.
我只是想找个人谈谈 莉娅
I just need someone to talk to, Lia.
老天哪 现在又是什么情况
Oh, God. Oh, man. What now?
-谁啊  -您好
- Hello? - Hi.
-我是奥利弗·努南  -好的
- Oliver Noonan. - Okay.
格丽·吉尔曼说你同意和我谈谈
Gerri Kellman said you agreed I could come talk to you?
知道了 抱歉 是谁放你进来的
Right. Sorry, who buzzed you in?
我们在听证会那次见过面的
We met at the hill hearings.
-没错 没错  -你好
- Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Hey. - Hey.
-对 对  -没错
- Yeah. Yeah. - Yeah.
-没错 我... 我记起来了  -没错
- Yes. I... Yeah, I remember. - Yeah...
当时我们有很多人在那吧
There were a lot of us, right? Yeah.
我是受阿比斯诺特·韦斯委托来的
Like, I'm a lawyer from Arbuthnot Weiss,
想过来和你打个招呼
and I'm just checking in to say hi.
那太好了 需要我支付费用吗
That's nice. Am I paying for this?
不用 律师费已经由韦斯达支付过了
No. My fees are paid by Waystar.
我能进去 好好...和你解释一下吗
Should I come in and... and... and explain?
-我可以...  -不好意思 稍等一下 是谁...
- I can... - Wait. Sorry. From... Sorry.
-是韦斯达委托的吗 还是洛根委托的...  -不是 都不是
- From Waystar? So from Logan or... - No. No.
我是受阿比斯诺特·韦斯委托来的 格雷格 放松点
I'm from Arbuthnot Weiss. Greg, keep up man.
没什么 我只是过来问问
Hey, no, I'm just checking
最近有没有联邦调查局的过来联系过你
in to see if the FBI has been in contact
或是你有没有什么问题
and see if you have any questions.
好的
Okay.
所以说你是...
Because you're...
我是你的律师
I'm your lawyer
-好  -没问题吧
- Okay. - right? Yeah?
-对  -所以我给... 我给格丽打通电话
- Yeah. - So I'll just... I'll call Gerri
跟她说我们这边已经没问题了
and tell her that we're all squared away.
要是有政府人员联系的话
And if the government calls,
她就可以转告他们说 我将为你辩护
then she can tell them that I represent you.
你能... 你能稍等一会吗
Can... can you... can you hold for one moment?
-没问题  -好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
-没问题  -稍等... 稍等一会
- Yeah. - Just... just hang... hang in. Hang tight.
-没问题  -稍后 稍后再给你回复
- Yeah. - And we'll, we'll seal the deal.
外面来了一个律师
So there is a lawyer here,
莉娅 他跟我说... 他是我的律师
Lia, and... so he's saying he is my lawyer.
你觉得他是我的律师吗
Do you think he's probably my lawyer?
我不确定 我... 我怎么知道
Well, I... I don't... I don't know.
他应该不能... 比如说 起诉我...
He couldn't, like, sue me or not...
逮捕我或传唤我出庭什么的吗
arrest me or subpoena me or...
我... 我真的不确定
I don't... I don't know...
我对这些东西真的一窍不通
I don't really know what any of it means.
需要我发消息问问我的教授吗
You want me to text my professor?
当然 问... 问一下他
Yeah. Text... text him. Text him.
兄弟 我觉得可以 我感觉...
Yo. Yeah, man. I think it's good. I feel...
我觉得... 我有些问题
I feel, like, uh, just a couple quick, quick questions
是你选的我 还是我选的你
which is, do you choose me or do I choose you?
格雷格 是你选的我
No, well, you choose, Greg.
那你可以先回去 然后...
Let's let you go now, and... and...
我要想一下 我只是需要...
and I'm gonna think. I just need
我需要再思考一下 再见
to think a little bit and just, uh, see you soon.
-好的  -不 不是...
- Well, okay. Good. - No, no, no, no. Not...
-这个承诺没有法律效力  -好的
- Not that that constitutes a legal promise. - All right.
-好的  -好的 我会打给格丽的
- All right. - Okay. All right. I'll call Gerri.
-好的 我会先打给格丽的  -好
- I'll call Gerri first. Okay. - Okay.
我知道你很忙
I know you have things going on
但我需要你赶快腾出八到十个小时的时间
but I'm gonna need you for like eight to ten hours very soon.
你随时都有可能收到传票 我们需要做好准备
You could get a subpoena anytime and we need to be ready.
好的 但是我现在没空 我有更大的鱼要钓
Okay. Uh, I can't do that right now. I have bigger fish.
比不进监狱更大的鱼吗
Bigger fish than staying out of prison?
我会发短信告诉你时间
Look, I'll message you a time.
在我们谈话之前
And ahead of our interview,
我需要仔细过一遍这些文件
I need to look over these papers in detail
然后我们就要谈谈政府需要得到什么信息以及在什么时间
and then we can talk through what the government gets and when.
-让我想想  -肯
- Let me think. - Ken, the FBI
联邦调查局现在就会出现在你家门口
maybe showing up at your door now.
他们可能正在申请对你公寓的搜查令
They could be getting a search warrant for your apartment.
要了解全局 你听到什么风声了吗
Big picture. What are you hearing?
你爸在启动政治操纵
Well, your dad is pushing political buttons.
据说他会来硬的 不合作 那就太好了
There's talk he might play hardball and not cooperate, which would be amazing.
因为那真的是个很拉跨的决定
I mean, that's just a really terrible, terrible decision.
如果他叫停这一切呢
What if he shuts this all down?
他没办法叫停这一切
He can't shut it down.
他可以的 他也许会的
Oh, yes, he can. I mean, he might.
你需要为所有可能出现的结果做好准备
You need to prepare for all eventualities. We might need to...
我们可能需要打给州警察来逮捕联邦调查局
to call the state police to arrest the FBI.
我们可能需要计划用一辆没有机尾数字的飞机
We might need to plan to fly me out without a tail number to...
-把我送到法兰克福或者委内瑞拉  -好的
- to Frankfurt or Venezuela. - Yeah.
这我开玩笑的 但我刚才说的都是认真的
I'm not serious, okay? But I am serious.
-喂  - 喂 你怎么样
- Hey. - "Hey, how goes it?"
我挺好的 怎么了 发生什么了吗
Yeah. Good. Fine. Why? What's up?
只是想问问你在哪
Just, um, wondering where you are.
我吗 我在家里
Me? I'm at home.
休息一会儿
"Just taking five."
好的
Okay.
只是关心一下 看看你怎么样了
Well, just checking in, seeing how you are.
你介意格丽当权吗
Uh, do you mind about Gerri?
什么 格丽吗 我不介意 没事的
Uh, what? No. Gerri? No. It's fine.
只是... 又一个羞辱罢了
It's, uh, just, uh, another fucking humiliation.
去你丫的
好吧 如果有什么大事记得跟我说
Well... yeah. Talk to me if there's big stuff.
我会的
Uh-huh. Will do.
谢谢你关心我 我爱你
Thanks for checking in and, you know, I love you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你... 你也爱我吗
And do you... do you love me too?
-怎么这么问  -什么怎么这么问
- "Why?" - Why?
怎么突然关心这件事了
Why do you wanna know?
什么鬼 我只觉得
The fuck? I just feel like it's a pretty
知道你爱不爱我还挺重要的
important thing to know whether you do or not.
你不能拿走我的爱 然后存起来
You know, you can't just take my love and bank it,
再时不时看看爱情市场
and then take a view of the
然后决定要不要继续投资我的爱
love market and see if you wanna invest in me.
但是 是的 我爱你
But, um, yeah, I do.
我爱你
I do.
好的 因为我也爱你
Great. Because I do too.
谢谢你 我很庆幸...
Thank you. It's good to know we...
我们的爱情投资组合是均衡的
we don't have an unbalanced love portfolio.
我爱你
I love you.
快来瞧瞧
Okay. Well, lookey-lookey here.
谁在这坐着呢
Who's all this then, huh?
-你好  -你好 我他妈见鬼了
- Hi. - Hi. Okay. Well, fuck me.
我想问问 但算了吧
I wondered but all right. Okay.
-他怎么样  -他怎么样吗
- Uh, how is he? - How is he?
-对  -他在想你他妈在哪儿
- Yeah. - He's wondering where the fuck you are.
你怎么不接电话
How come you're not picking up?
我关机了
Oh, I've had my phone off.
不是故意的
No agenda.
不是故意的 一点也没有吗
No agenda? None at all?
他怎么样
How is he?
他...
He's fucking, you know...
他挺好的 格丽正在研究怎么在菲律宾买个私人小岛
he's fine, I guess. Gerri's looking into how it works
就是挺常规的事
to buy a private island in the Philippines, so regular stuff.
你到底在搞什么鬼
What is your fucking game?
怎么了 你在搞什么鬼
Why? What's yours?
我来这儿找你
I'm here looking for you.
当然了 我信了
Yeah. Oh, sure. Sure.
据你所知 事实就他妈是这样
As far as you know, that's the fucking truth.
真的 我听到脚步声了
It's true. I'm hearing footsteps.
他来了 想引起别人注意的小婊子
Oh, here he comes. The attention whore.
小罗
Hey, Rome.
-你好  -你最近怎么样
- Hello. - How you doing?
谢谢你的关心 我很好
Oh, thank you for asking. I'm great.
事实上 这几天真的很不错
It's just been like a really great few days, actually.
你呢 你怎么样
How about you, how you doin'?
我感觉很好
I feel pretty good.
有一些遗憾 但是 感觉被净化了
Certain amount of regret but, you know, pretty cleansed.
净化了 真有意思
Cleansed? That's interesting.
听上去真他妈有意思
That's like really fucking interesting.
那我猜如果想知道你的真实近况
I guess if I wanted to know how you're actually doing,
还得等你
I'd have to wait for you to, you know,
再他妈开个全国新闻发布会
call a national fucking press conference,
你就会说 "虽然我说了我很好
and you'd be like, "No, I said I was fine,
但其实我不太好
but actually I'm not fine."
罗曼是个屌人
"Roman is a dick, and he
他下飞机都没给我带什么礼物
didn't even bring me anything from the airport."
现在我感觉很糟糕"
"Now I feel bad."
实际上 我给你带了东西
I did, actually. I brought you
不知道哪儿产的丹麦肉桂
those Danish cinnamon things from the wherever place.
-那简直...  -那个...
- Oh, that's... - The... the...
你真好 谢谢你
That's sweet. That is so kind. Thank you.
闭嘴吧 爱吃不吃
Oh, shut up. Just eat them or don't.
不用谢
You're welcome.
你看了吗
You take a look?
我看了 去你丫的
Oh, yeah. Fuck you too.
所以 家人们 咱们能重新来过吗
Yeah. So, look, guys, can we clean slate this?
你们不喜欢我对老爸做的事
You didn't like how I did what I did to dad.
随你们的便吧 对不起
Sure. Whatever. I'm sorry.
但那是我和他之间的事
You know, that's for me and him.
而且目前的情况是
But here's the thing.
他已经玩儿完了
He's over, so let's work
我们联手起来接管公司 让他安心地养老吧
together to take over and help him move on out.
关于这个 我只是来监视小西的 所以...
Um, well, I'm just here to spy on this one, so...
而我是过来给你打退堂鼓的
And I'm just here to get you to back down.
抱歉
Sorry.
不好意思 我很想说你他妈有多烂
I'm sorry, I wanna tell you what a fucking prick you are,
但能换个地方吗
but can we do it where
换个不用跟拉瓦的遛狗人挤在一起的地方
we don't have to fold in Rava's dog walker?
可以 抱歉 跟我来
Yeah. Sorry. Yeah. Follow me.
-索菲的房间  -你不记得自己娃儿的名字吗
- Sophie's room. - You don't remember this kid's name?
呃... 索菲... 索菲的房间
"Uh, uh, Sophie... Sophie's room."
停在这儿就好 谢谢你 我会五星好评的
Okay. Just here. Thank you. Five stars.
外公 谢谢你愿意见我
Hey, Gramps. Oh, thanks for this.
大都市的老外公
Big Gramps in the big city.
你最近怎么样 你... 你在这儿干嘛
Hey, how you doing? What... what are you doing here?
我在处理一些自己的事情
I am putting my affairs in order.
很好 很好
Very nice. Very nice.
你那位不愿抛头露面
Your publicity shy friend,
畏首畏尾的朋友 一直在联系我
the shrinking violet, has been calling me.
他想要什么
What does he want?
是肯德尔 我觉得...
Kendall. Well, so I...
我觉得他很大程度上跟你是一队的
I think he's very much on the same page as you.
我希望这听上去不会显得过于美好 让你不相信
If it doesn't sound too basic to be like good, right?
让公司变好 诸如此类的 我觉得这...
Make the company nice and so on, which... which I guess is...
我觉得这也是你的主张吧
that's kind of your thing, right?
在我看来 他的表现装腔作势 华而不实
I found his performance histrionic and meretricious.
展开说说呢
Well, tell me about it.
他是个自负的利己主义者
The man is a self-regarding popinjay.
可能是吧
No, sure.
我只是不想家丑外扬
I just don't like seeing dirty laundry washed in public.
对啊 我也是
Right? Uh, yeah.
这就是我为什么...
And that's... and that's actually why...
我为什么想跟你聊聊
why I wanted to chat with you.
我想在这场战争中正确地站边
I just wanna chart the right course through this whole thing.
洛根给我提供了律师
And Logan's offering me a
肯德尔也给我提供了律师
lawyer and Kendall's offering me a lawyer.
而我想要...
And I just, you know, I'm try...
我需要独立的法律建议
I think I could use some independent legal advice.
格雷格 你为什么需要请律师呢
Why do you need a lawyer, Greg?
我也什么没做什么错事
I mean, I haven't done anything wrong.
我... 我只是觉得
I... I... I just think
如果每个人在这场战争中都穿了盔甲
if everyone's showing up to battle in armor,
我现在赤身裸体 毫无防备
then I feel kind of expose here in my loincloth.
看起来就很糟糕
Bad visual.
好
Yes.
什么
Yes?
我可以帮你 格雷格
Yes, I can back you, Greg.
我帮你请法律顾问
I'll set you up with legal counsel.
谢谢 谢谢外公 那... 抱歉
Thank you. Thank you, Gramps. So... Yeah. Sorry. Sorry.
-够了够了 我会再跟你联系  -谢谢你
- That'll do. I'll call you. - Thank you.
-好 你真是我的救星  -不会太久
- All right. You're the man. - Soon.
我爱你
I love you.
好了 别碰她的东西
Okay. Don't touch any of her shit.
好了 我要说的很简单
Okay. So, uh, it's pretty simple.
我们联合起来反抗爸 把他拉下马
Let's gang up on dad and take him down.
天啊 至少等我先关上门吧
Jesus, let me shut the door first.
好吧 那你之前怎么没来找我们
Okay. Well, why didn't you come to us before?
对吧 现在情况一团糟
Yeah? This is a real fucking mess now.
我很晚才想到这主意
It came together for me in my head late and,
而且 这不是...
uh, you know, it wasn't...
我... 我知道我要做什么但...
I... I knew what I was gonna do but...
你是临时起意吗
That was spontaneous?
我和律师咨询过
Well, I spoke with a lawyer.
-这样啊 你咨询过律师  -是 但...
- Okay. You spoke with a lawyer? - Yeah. But...
但事实上 他们极力反对 我是说...
but they advised against, essentially. I mean, I...
我... 我不想复述他们的话 但....
I... and don't wanna rehash it all but...
我实际上是单打独斗
look, I was effectively acting alone.
好一个经过律师全盘指导
Right. A spontaneous,
临时起意的真情流露
heart-felt outpouring of thoroughly lawyered emotion.
随便你们怎么看我
You guys can think whatever you want, in the end, of me.
好吧 你把局势搞得太复杂了
Okay. Well, you've made this very hard.
但我来这里是为了弄明白
But I'm here to find out
你想要什么 然后劝你回头是岸
what you want and to get you to back down.
是的 代表老爸
Yeah. On dad's behalf.
好的 好
Oh, right. Right. Right.
那要是我说 我就是要
So if I say, I'm taking him
把他拉下马 任何条件我都不感兴趣
down and I'm not interested in any deals with him,
你就... 打电话告诉他 然后拍拍屁股走人吗
you just... you call and tell him, and just take a hike?
对
Yeah.
-他来了  -谁来了
- He's here. - Who's here?
-康纳 让他进来  -好
- Connor. Send him in. - Right.
怪不得我刚听见小丑车靠边停车呢
I thought I heard a clown car pulling up.
理想情况是我们四个一起露面接受媒体采访
Ideally I'd like to make a media appearance all four of us.
-是吗  -真有趣
- Oh, would you? - Oh, sweet.
我们要穿上你设计的戏服吗 混球
Are we gonna be wearing costumes that you've designed, asshole?
你想都别想
Yeah. That's just not gonna happen.
很好
Okay.
-谢谢你过来  -老康
- Well... Thanks for coming. - Hey, Con.
人都到齐了
Here we all are.
老爸正找你俩呢
You know, Pop's looking for you two.
我们是代表他过来的
Yeah. We're here on his behalf.
当然了 亲爱的 我也是
Oh, sure thing, honey. Me too.
都是为了老爸 我们才在这团聚
All about dad. That's why we're all here.
好了 我们能不能开诚布公 好好聊聊
Okay. Can... can we, uh, turn off the devices and get into this?
所以... 我的想法是 如果现在的乱局
So... my thing is if this shit was
只是附带现象 那还可以一笔带过
just epiphenomenal, maybe it could be written out.
但这些事件只是表面症状 背后是潜藏在
But these incidents are symptomatic of a foundational sickness
我们父亲和他公司里的沉疴痼疾
within our father and his company.
他的口技比二十块一发的鸡还棒
Don't he use that tongue prettier than a 20-dollar whore?
行 你的重点是什么
Yeah. Like, what's your point?
我是说已经烂到根上了
My point is the milk is going sour.
原来如此
Well, that explains it.
那些... 伟大的白人 从政坛到文化层面
You know, the... the Great Whites, from politics to culture,
他们正退出历史舞台 这是我们的时代
they're rolling off stage. It's our time.
你是说 我们这个多种族跨性别
Oh, you mean, us, this multi-fucking-ethnic transgender alliance
二十多岁的梦想家联盟走上了历史舞台
of 20-something dreamers we got right here?
宏观角度来看
Okay. Big picture.
我们处在漫长美国时代的末期
We're at the end of the long American century.
我们的公司就是衰亡帝国中的衰亡帝国
Our company is a declining empire inside a declining empire.
太对了 兄弟
Amen, brother.
人们正...
People are... are...
用枪和毒品自我戕害
killing themselves with
堕落的速度快到让我们跟不上节奏
guns or dope so fast that we're losing pace.
取关了
Unsubscribe.
我们是死而不僵的百足之虫
We're... we're fat-fingered fucks
靠着剩余脂肪苟延残喘
and we can only live on cream.
美国的超级霸权日渐式微
US supremacy is waning.
我想的是 在这样的大背景下
What I think is, within that context,
我们可以重新定位 变身跨国企业
we can become omni-national and reposition.
因为无论是文化还是物质层面 我们都没被绑定
Because actually we are not tied, culturally or physically.
所以... 事实上 我们正处在跨越式发展的绝佳时机
So... so we are actually in a great position to leapfrog tech.
在下一个世纪
Information is going to be
信息将成为比水还贵的资源
more precious than water in the next hundred.
整合我们所有的新闻业务
Combine all our news operations,
成为全球新闻资讯中心
become the global news information hub.
亚马逊已经二十岁高龄了 盖茨是个老古董
Amazon is 20 years old. Gates is an old geezer.
为我们的品牌刮骨疗毒 可以实现飞速发展
Detoxify our brand and we can go supersonic.
怎么样 有兴趣加入吗
So what do you say? Are we interested?
只是这里面背叛老爸的部分
You know, there's just something about betraying our father
让我很难接受
that just doesn't sit well with me.
他就是那个
He's a central player in
吞噬了美式民主核心的...
a rotten cabal that has basically eaten...
腐朽阴谋里的第一大蛀虫
the heart out of American democracy.
腐朽阴谋做乐队名还不错
Rotten cabal is a good name for a band.
他是不会因为这个受审的 肯
He's not gonna be on trial for that though, Ken.
或许他该受到审判
Well, maybe he should be.
你明白吗 就算不是他
You know, but if he didn't do it,
也会有别人用同样的伎俩赚同样的脏钱
it would have been someone else making the same dollar off the same shit.
-或许吧 或许吧  -是啊
- Maybe. Yeah, maybe. - Yeah.
或许... 都和我们无关
Ma... Maybe we're all irrelevant.
或许集中营永远不会消失
You know, maybe there were always going to be death camps
或许这个星球马上就要炸了 我们什么都做不了
and maybe the planet is going to fry and there's nothing we can do.
又或许 人们可以做出改变
Or maybe people make a difference.
我不知道 你觉得... 人类的命运重要吗
I don't know. Do... do you think human beings matter?
我准备直说 我是个间谍
You know, I'm just gonna say right out that I'm a spy.
我要回去把你的话全告诉他
I'm gonna go back and tell him everything.
我跟老爸同一阵线 所以 去你的吧
I'm with dad. So, yeah, fuck you.
没事 没事 我其实也不在乎 我...
Fine. Fine. I... I don't actually give a fuck. You know, I'm...
我一个人就可以搞定
I can perfectly well do this alone.
我只是想对你们开诚布公...
I'm actually just trying to be openhearted and...
才把你们请过来
and invite you in here.
毕竟 我单干可能还更容易点
I mean, it would probably be simpler to go alone
但是我他妈想给你们一张逃生舱的船票
but I want to offer you a fucking ticket to the escape pod.
这家伙真他妈善良啊
Nice fucking guy, huh?
他把你踩在脚下 指派格丽挑大梁 你很满意吗
You're happy he went over your head and put in Gerri?
我觉得格丽是个不错的人选 很满意
I think that Gerri is a good choice, yeah.
-怎么了  -没什么 你就护着老爸
- What? - Whatever. Defend dad all you want,
-但格丽可以顾好自己  -对 我知道
- but Gerri can look after herself. - Yeah, I know that.
我没有护着格丽 我是说...
I'm not defending Gerri. I'm saying...
你没法跟妈咪一起躲在保护伞下面
You can't hide under the covers with mommy.
妈的闭嘴 西沃恩
Oh, fuck off, Shivan.
你喜欢给所有人看你的小弟弟
You love showing your pee-pee to everyone,
但你要知道总有一天 你得拿它操点什么
but someday you know you're actually gonna have to fuck something.
-操你大爷 疯批  -小罗...
- Fuck you. Bitch. - Rom...
-干嘛 别管我  -小罗 就...
- What? Leave it. - Rom, just...
-怎么了  -小罗
- What? - Rom?
好了 我会... 这招太低级了
Okay. Fine. I'll... That was low.
是他反应过激了 我又没怎么样
That was an overreaction. That was not.
我们就不能尽量心平气和地聊吗
Can we just try to keep this nice? Yeah?
他的性癖奇怪又不是我的错 我很刻薄吗
It's not my fault he's got a sex thing. Was I too harsh?
开什么玩笑 他就爱这样
Are you kidding? He loves it.
他会穿上我前妻的内裤在外面自慰
He'll be out there jerking off wearing my ex-wife's panties.
-欢迎来到萨拉热窝  -谢谢
- Welcome to Sarajevo. - Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你那些犯浑的孩子...  -我知道
- Those fucking kids of yours... - I know.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
我很好
I'm okay.
现在不是和我疏远的时候 玛西娅
It's not a good time to be estranged, Marcia.
小孩 代理人战争
Boy. Proxy battle.
我很受伤 洛根
I was very hurt, Logan.
我知道
I know.
所以呢
So?
我不能吃瘪 玛西娅
I can't eat shit, Marcia.
我做不到
I just can't.
但是...
But...
你是个笨蛋
You're a fool.
我有时候会... 心烦意乱
I can sometimes get... distracted.
当然 我或许会想和某人聊一聊
Of course, I might like to have small conversation with somebody.
-这边走 晚上好 玛西娅  -晚上好
- This way. Good evening, Marcia. - Good evening.
-欢迎  -非常感谢
- Welcome. - Thank you very much.
对不起
Sorry.
道什么歉 我刚去了卫生间
For what? I went to the bathroom.
我才不在乎
I don't give a shit.
你个贱人
You whore.
好的 我是这么看的
Okay. Here's how I see this.
老爸很复杂...
Dad is complicated...
但他也曾做过 或者说没有阻止坏事发生 不是吗
but he did or let bad stuff happen. Yeah?
这就成了我们一部分的原罪
And now it's a part of us and our sickness.
因为我们知情 我们得负起责任
And we have to take responsibility because we knew
现在我们有机会
and this is our chance to
洗心革面 偿还债务
pay our dues and wash our hands for absolution.
行吧 但我不知情
Uh, okay. Well, I didn't know.
随你怎么说 但你知情
Sure, whatever, but yeah, you did.
不 我是真的不知道
Uh, no, I... I... I didn't.
小罗 你知道吗
Did you, Rom?
不 我不知道
No, I didn't. No. No.
-你不知道吗  -不知道
- No? - No.
那些遭人利用和剥削的可怜舞者源源不断被输送过来
The fucking pipeline of sad dancers who got used and abused
还他妈允诺说能去好莱坞 我们都知道真相
and promised some Hollywood bullshit. We fucking knew.
好 我大概知道...
Right. No, I... I mean, I kind of knew...
有这些事...
you know, that there was...
但我不知道这操蛋... 我真的不知道
but I didn't know to the fucking... I didn't. I really did not.
拜托 我们都知道好吗
Oh, come on. We knew.
-什么  -我们他妈的都知情
- What? - We fucking knew, okay?
我不想再瞎扯了 好吗 我受够了
And I... and I... I don't like bullshit, okay? I'm done. Enough.
-好 但我们到底知道多少  -对啊
- Well, okay, but what did we know? - Yeah.
小西 我不是说有你的责任
I'm not saying that you're responsible, Shiv,
但是爸 老莫 "狼群"这些人
but the guys, Dad, Mo, the wolf pack.
我们是知道的
We knew.
从侮辱女性的玩笑和氛围...
The jokes and the vibe to women and to the...
到那些管理邮轮业务的下流肥臀们
to the grubby fat asses who took the cruises,
那些视而不见和封口费的行为
the blind eye, and the payoffs,
老爸的他兄弟们 那些不可告人的秘密
and the hush-hush about dad's pals,
或是 那些被压榨的外国劳工...
or foreign workers who got crushed like...
就他妈像绞肉机里的碎肉
like meat in a fucking grinder
他们未经任何训练 藏在酒桶里偷渡过来
with zero training, and the border barrel,
还有解决掉任何泄密的叛徒
and clean out the rats in the hold.
不 这都不是我们的错
And, you know, no, it wasn't our fault.
如果你只想自扫门前雪
And you want to pretend your shit doesn't stink,
我不会阻挡你 但是我们...
be my guest, but... but we...
-我们知道 我们知道那些家伙  -谢谢你
- We knew. We knew what those guys - Thank you.
聚在老爸书房时 他们在笑什么
in dad's study were laughing about.
不 我不知道舞者要卖身才能得到工作
Oh, no, I didn't know the dancers were fucking for their jobs.
我也不知道我们他妈的把非法移民丢下船
And I didn't know that we threw fucking migrants off boats
还利用公司隐私政策掩盖真相
and covered it up as a matter of secret company policy.
不 我不知道他们当时在笑什么
No, I didn't know what they were laughing about.
-别和老莫一起去游泳池  -对啊
- Don't get in the pool with Mo. - Yeah.
所以我没和任何一个老变态去过游泳池
I didn't get in the pool with any of those fucking creeps.
因为他让一伙变态管理邮轮业务
Yeah, because he'd let a gang of creeps run cruises.
不 肯德尔 因为我当时才十五岁
No, Kendall, 'cause I was 15.
好吧 那你现在知道真相了吧
Yeah, well, you know now, right?
-你现在知道了吧  -那当然 现在我当然知道了
- Do you know now? - Of course, I fucking know now.
好吧 这些都是次要的 好吗
Okay. This is all a sidebar. Okay?
我们... 我只求
We... all I am asking is for
我们能从真相出发 往前走
us to move forward from a position of truth.
如果我们不接受这唯一的真相
And are we excluded from the
就要被关在天堂门外了吗
kingdom of heaven unless we accept the one true truth?
孩子们要... 我得先...
Look, the kids are... I'll go...
我得去抱抱孩子们 好吗
uh, I just wanna hug my kids. Okay?
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
我们别再追根究底了 好吗
We don't even need to get into this. Okay?
都是无关紧要的屁事
This is side shit.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
谢谢你送的马 兄弟 非常幽默
Thanks for the horse, man. Pretty funny.
对 我原本想送个真的 一颗马头
Yeah. Well, I wanted to send a real one. Well, a severed head.
但过审需要的文件太多了
But you wouldn't believe the paperwork.
听着 抱歉我没能...
Look, sorry I couldn't... you know,
提前通知你关于发布会的事
fold you in or alert you on the press conference.
老兄 我有幸见证越南修道士点火自燃
Dude, I got to see the Vietnamese monk set himself on fire.
还有地球上最大怪奇秀的入场券
I got a ticket to the greatest freak show on Earth.
所以... 怎么样 从你的角度来说...
So... so, look, how does this play? From the point of view of...
你真的有证据
Do you actually have a case?
对 我保证
Yes. I can kill it.
好 我们洗耳恭听
Okay. Good. We're all ears.
但我觉得没有意义 兄弟
But I don't see it, dude.
先聊聊吧
Let's talk.
你好 桑蒂 谢谢你专程赶来
Hey, Sandi, thanks for coming over.
确实不是很方便
It wasn't terribly convenient.
不是吗 好吧
No? Well, sure.
丢掉代理人票对你和你父亲来说也不方便吧
I guess, nor would losing the proxy vote for you and your dad.
爸 你可以说话了
Dad, you're on.
桑迪
Hey, Sandy.
-你好  -好 听着
- "Hello." - Okay. Look
我可以长篇大论两小时 两分钟 或只要两个词
so I can give you two hours, two minutes, or two words.
长话短说比较好
Ooh, shorter's better.
支持我
Back me.
有点过于短了
Well, maybe a little more.
听着 桑迪
Look, Sandy, we all know
你虽然口是心非 但你确实
you are kind of not really but, yeah, really
想要打败我爸
doing this to beat my dad.
我父亲不这样做事
My father doesn't operate that way.
他这么做是因为商业利益
He's in this because of the business fundamentals.
当然 那当然
Sure. Sure.
我们在希腊给斯图伊的条件
Well, look, the offer we made Stewy in Greece
仍然有效
we stick with all that,
而且 还少了我爸的干扰 对吧
but, plus, my dad's gone, yeah?
当时我爸答应给你们董事会席位等等
And when my dad offers you the board seats and all,
他会用各种招数 使你们边缘化
one way or another, he's gonna sideline you, right?
但我们团队提供的战略调整 是货真价实的
But when my team offers a strategic review, we mean it.
所以肯 你今天想得到什么
And what do you want today, Ken?
今天我... 只想跟你们谈谈
Today, I just... I just want the conversation,
并达成一个共识 假设我们推翻我爸
and... and an understanding if we push him out,
我们就能避免一场股东投票战争
then we can avoid a, uh, you know, contested shareholder vote.
卡洛丽娜
玛西娅 我们都很开心你回来了
"Hi, Marcia. Everyone's so happy you're back."
卡洛丽娜
很好 我也很开心
Good. I'm very happy.
卡洛丽娜
我们可以谨慎地商讨一下措辞
"We were thinking we could discreetly agree some words"
关于最近你去哪了 以及这段关系的情况
"In terms of, um where you've been and where the relationship is at."
-当然可以  -太好了
- Of course. - Great.
关于这件事的观点 如果你能接受的话
And in terms of the optics on this, if you'd find it acceptable,
我们希望还原大众一个熟悉的洛根形象
we would love to get back visually to the Logan that we all know
而你身为洛根的妻子陪同他去往...
and his wife back by his side so that if we fly or if we go...
当然 我有一些要求
Obviously, I have some requests.
好 好吧
Oh, okay. Right.
他对那个女人的迷恋 让我蒙羞
I was quite humiliated by his infatuation with that woman.
卡洛丽娜 你想...
Karolina, do you wanna...
不 雨果 你说吧
"No, you go ahead, Hugo."
我认为洛根的立场 毋庸置疑的是...
I mean, I think Logan's position, and it's the truth, is that...
我被羞辱了 所以应当有所补偿
I was humiliated and things must be made right.
无须多言
Nothing needs to be said.
当时他用下半身思考
He was led by his prick.
我们知道他们之间什么事都没有发生
Because we really would say that nothing ever happened.
她是个妓女 她没能完成她的工作 不是我的问题
She's a whore and it's not my problem if she wouldn't finish him.
懂了 我明白了
Got it. Got the message.
所以 如果要我公众现身
So for my return to be public,
我要看到信托上有我的名字
I will need my role on the trust finalized,
阿米尔的未来有所保障
Amir's prospects assured,
我的女儿有人关照
my daughter taken care of,
以及我的财务地位有所提升
and improvements in my financial position.
塞莱斯特会跟你谈妥细节的
Celeste will deal with the details.
谢谢你
Thank you.
好 我接下来开的价
Now, the numbers I'm going to
听起来会像是个天文数字
propose will sound like very, very large numbers,
但若是考虑到在危机四伏的股东大会前
but if you consider them in terms of the difficulties it would present Mr. Roy
发布难堪的离婚声明会对洛根先生造成何种伤害
to have an acrimonious divorce announced ahead of a contested shareholder meeting,
这个价码会显得十分合理
then they start to seem like very reasonable numbers.
我当然担心
I do worry.
你保证过你那儿是储藏上等红酒的最佳机构
I was assured that yours is the best facility for the storage of fine wines,
但现在我看到一份地质检测报告 我很担心
but now I'm looking at a geological survey and it's worrying me.
所以呢
So?
什么
What?
你什么想法
Where you at?
听听他说的 然后向上报告
Just, uh, hear him out and report, right?
-当然 我们得保护好老爸  -对
- Right. Oh, yeah. We gotta protect dad. - Yeah.
如果我们背后捅刀 他肯定难逃一死 所以...
Because if we knifed him now, it's true he would bleed out, so...
这我不确定
I don't know about that.
这当然是真的
Well, it's just true.
我不确定我想要胡乱推测
Well, I'm not sure I care to speculate.
不 这是既定事实
No, it was just a statement of fact.
是吗
Is it now?
是啊
Yeah.
那你为什么要对我挤眉弄眼
Well, then why are you making fuck-y eyes at me?
-我才没有  -有 你有
- I'm not making fuck-y eyes at you. - Yeah, you are.
-你在挤眉弄眼 像这样...  -什么鬼...
- You're making fuck-y eyes. You're like... - What are fuck-y...
-这样...  -我眼神是这样吗
- Like... - Oh, those are my eyes?
-难逃一死  -我靠
- "Bleed out" - Jesus!
有点像好吗 别再胡说八道了
A little bit though. Stop trying to convince me of shit.
甚至都不会发生
It's not necessarily true even.
别人有可能 但爸才不会
Maybe someone else, but this is dad.
他可是大白鲸
And he's like fucking Moby Dick.
即使被鱼叉刺中也不耽误他把我们大卸八块
He could take us all down with his back riddled with harpoons.
-我们仨全部  -对啊
- A... All three of us? - Yeah.
包括老康
And Con?
只要我们都支持肯 他就完了
We back Ken, no, he's toast.
我不是说我们应该这么做
I'm not saying we should do it.
只是我们需要决定
We just need to decide what
下一步该怎么做 因为现在是关键时刻
the fuck we're gonna do because this is a moment.
你觉得呢
I mean, what do you think?
先是瑞亚 现在又是格丽
Uh, first Rhea. Now Gerri.
这… 事态不妙
Uh, it doesn't... it's not great.
我不知道 我觉得爸不会下台
Well, I don't know, I don't think dad would actually go.
你觉得呢 老康
Do you, Con?
他并不是无懈可击 小罗
He's not infallible, Rom.
当然不是 我只是觉得他从没失败过 以后也不会
No. Sure. I just don't think he ever fails or ever will.
他…什么 他总是在犯错
He... What? He missteps all the time.
他已经不是二十年前那样了
He's not dad from 20 years ago.
他是... 他是现在的爸
He's... he's now dad.
如果我们联合起来
It's very hard to imagine
支持肯德尔 很难想象他还能保住地位
him surviving if we allied and backed Kendall.
是的 没错
Yes. Exactly.
如果我们再跟弗兰克和卡尔联手 他必死无疑了
And if we squared Frank and Karl, then he is toast.
我不知道 也许吧
I don't know. Maybe.
肯定的啊
Yes-by.
-但那是他的董事会  -是的 当然
- Uh, but it's his board. - Oh, yeah. Oh. Sure.
但初生牛犊不怕虎
But a lot of fresh blood is a lot of fear.
如果我们今天倒戈
I think if we pulled the pin today,
明天董事会就会人心惶惶 我们就有了胜算
tomorrow, a spooked board, we could win.
我唯一担心的是 这可能真的会要了他的命
My only concern with that, it might actually kill him.
好了 讨论得怎么样了
Okay. How we doing?
刚说到哪里了
So where are we?
好吧 即使你赢了 让爸下台 我…
All right. Look, you win, take dad out, I...
我觉得我们也未必能在代理权战争中胜出
I don't see us coming through in the proxy battle.
股东不喜欢混乱局面
Shareholders, they don't like confusion.
我们家族要如何掌握控制权
How does the family stay in control?
我们给爸一把手枪
We give dad the revolver,
带他去办公室 代理权战争就此结束
show him to his office, proxy battle is over.
桑迪和斯图伊会让步 我和他们谈过了
Sandi and Stewy would back down. I've spoken with them.
-还挺忙的嘛  -不需要投票
- Busy fucking bee. - No vote.
-我们达成协议了  -真的吗
- We have a settlement. - Really?
如果爸直接退位 没问题
I think if dad went fast, yeah.
各位 我不知道自己对爸到底是什么情感
Look, guys, I don't know what I think about dad.
爱恨交加
Uh, I love him. I hate him.
具体要让心理咨询师来解释了
I'm gonna outsource it to my therapist.
但他是打算送我去坐牢的 知道吗
But he was going to send me to jail, you know?
他也会这样对你的 小罗
And he'd do the same to you, Rom.
老康也是
And Con.
至于小西 我不知道
Shiv, I don't know.
我不知道 也许吧
I don't know. Maybe.
所以说实在的 我们欠他什么呢
So what do we owe him here, really?
好吧 如果我们超越了亚马逊
Well, what would the shape of this
会有一个什么样的新愿景
new fucking reality be anyway, us leapfrogging Amazon?
好 我们... 根本上像是 公元前323年
Yeah. Well, uh, we're... we're looking at, uh, 323 B.C., basically.
-当然了  -亚历山大死了
- Oh, yeah, naturally. - Alexander is dead.
我得到了亚洲
I take Asia.
你得到了埃及 小西得到了欧洲
You take Egypt. Shiv takes Europe.
-老康 剩余的国家  -好吧
- Con, the rest of the world. - Right.
-谢谢  -独立的部门
- Thanks. - Separate divisions.
我以首席执行官的名义进行监督
I could oversee us as CEO on
我们转型 在全球制造影响力
paper as we shift to these spheres of influence
在前进的过程中同步评估核心价值
and evaluate what is core as we move forward.
所以你要来监督我们
So you'll oversee us?
作为转型过程的必要部分...
Well, I'd offer my leadership initially as a... as a...
我可以贡献我的领导才能
you know, as a necessary part of a transformational process.
你会这样为我们牺牲吗
You would do that for us?
-老兄 我… 拜托  -你真是大方 谢谢你啊 肯
- Dude, I'm... Come on. - Oh, you're so generous. Thanks, Ken.
不 就你现在的处境而言 行不通的
Well, no, because in your position that just doesn't work.
-言过其实了  -言过其实
- It's a stretch. - It's a stretch.
这根本就是拿蛋蛋敲定音鼓
It's a fucking scrotum over a timpani drum.
如果要我支持你对抗爸 那就得由我来掌权
If I were to back you against dad, I would need to take over.
-什么 天啊  -开始了
- Uh, what? Whoa. - Here we go.
门儿都没有
Whoa, Nelly.
我也希望如此 但你没有经验
You know, I wish I could, but you don't have the experience,
所以现阶段还不行 我希望可以 但无能为力
so that's not possible right now. I wish it was but it isn't.
得了吧 你已经臭名昭著
Come on. You're a busted flush.
我是唯一能改革公司的人
I'm the only person who can reform.
你的争议性太强 大家都觉得你是...
You're too divisive. You're still seen...
虽然我不这么觉得
I don't see you this way,
但大家还是把你看作是
but you're still seen as a token
刚从象牙塔醒来的绣花公主 我不这样认为…
woman wonk woke snowflake. I don't think that...
-什么  -但市场这样认为
- What? - but the market does.
-胡说八道  -的确如此 我刚和市场通了电话
- Bullshit. - Well, it's true. I just spoke to the market.
市场就是这样认为的
That's exactly what the market thinks.
各位 只是临时职位 可以吗
Guys, interim chair. Okay?
新的管理团队 新官上任
New directors, clean broom,
然后我们再决定如何分享战果
and then we can figure out how to split the spoils.
我要去打几个电话
Uh, I have some calls to make.
我也确实有几个电话要打 所以…
Well, I actually do have some calls to make, so...
-跟这件事没关系  -都休息一会儿吧
- No. Unrelated. - Take a moment.
那这件事不能外传
But this stays in here, yeah?
-必须的  -是
- Absolutely. - Yeah.
行
Okay.
汤姆
Uh, hey, Tom.
你... 你说话方便吗
Can you, uh... can you talk?
-方便  -好
- Yeah. - Okay.
我和肯在一起
So I'm with Ken.
真的吗
You are?
你已经知道了吗
Did you know?
不只是 我… 我怎么会知道
No, I... no. Why would I know?
他… 他提出结盟
Uh, so he's... he's offering an alliance.
我 小罗 老康 联手扳倒爸
Me, Rom, Con, we take down dad.
我靠
Shit.
是的 是的
Yeah. Yeah.
-你怎么想  -我不知道...
- What do you think? - I don't know. Is...
他怎么样了 他没事吧
how is he? Is he okay?
他没事
"Uh, he's okay."
波斯尼亚人可能盼着我们早点走吧
Uh, the Bosnians want us to leave. Maybe.
操
"Fuck."
所以 该死 你...
So, fuck, what do you...
你觉得呢 如果我们有你和弗兰克的支持...
what do you think? If we got you, Frank...
是的 估计就宣判死刑了
Right. That's terminal, I guess.
那到时候会由谁来掌权呢
But then who ends up king potato?
是你吗
I... Is it you?
也许吧 我也不知道 我...
Uh, maybe. I don't know. I...
我谁也不是 这是问题所在
I mean, I'm nobody is the thing.
我没在公司上过班 甚至他妈的连个职务都没有
I've never worked in the company, and I don't even have a fucking job title.
但是...
What... but...
但你能看到未来 对吧
You can see it though, can't you?
-对  -你看得到
- Yeah. - You can see it.
-喂  -喂 格丽熊
- Yeah? - Hey, Gerr Bear.
我要把我的鸡巴
So I'm just gonna put my
放进你诡计多端的剪刀手里
dick in your mad scheming Scissorhands here.
罗曼...
Roman...
我在肯德尔家
I'm at Kendall's, and he
他想找我们一起扳倒爸
wants us to join up with him and take down dad.
如果成真了 对你来说是个噩梦
So, yeah. Nightmare for you if that happens.
但现在 先别想那么多 虽然你做不到
But for a moment, put that aside, which obviously you can't,
但如果我真这么做了 会怎么样
but if I do that, what happens?
如果你们联手操纵董事会
Um, if you all come out and work the board,
说实话 你爸爸就没戏了
honestly, yeah, I think that zaps your dad.
好吧 那你觉得应该由谁来接班
Right. And then who takes over, do you think?
肯德尔吗 我吗 还是小西
Is it... is it gonna be Kendall, or possibly me, Shiv?
都不行 你们都不合适 这是个烫手山芋
No, I don't think any of you come through. It's snake linguini.
可能要由桑迪来选
I mean, maybe Sandi picks. Maybe.
我不知道 但说实话 你们都不行
I don't know. But honestly, no.
你们都会遭殃的
I think you all get burnt.
但显然我不能相信你
But obviously I can't trust you.
我是说 你的折衷主义建议
I mean, your advice is so
已经完全没有价值了
compromised as to be completely worthless,
但 你有什么建议
but what is your advice?
跟着我吧 罗曼
Stick with me, Roman.
我们现在占据上风
We have something going.
况且你刚刚给我这个非常危险的敌人
And I'm an incredibly dangerous enemy
透露了对你不利的信息
to whom you've just imparted prejudicial information.
别恐吓我 格丽 我没时间打一发
Well, don't threaten me Gerri. I don't have time to jerk off.
那你打算怎么办
So what are you gonna do?
爸爸送了甜甜圈过来
Dad sent doughnuts.
-什么鬼  -爸爸送了一些
- What the fuck? - Dad has sent
完全无辜的甜甜圈过来 没下毒
some perfectly innocent and I'm sure safe-to-eat donuts.
想让我们办个愉快的茶话会
He wants us all to have a nice tea party.
-真有他的  -好了
- Beautiful. - Yeah.
他会知道的 必然会
He's gonna know. Of course, he is.
是你告诉他的吗
Well, did you tell him?
小西 什么意思
Shiv, come on.
我为什么要告诉他
Why would I tell him?
好吧... 我不会吃的
Well... I wouldn't.
当然没毒... 是的 我是说...
I mean, no, of course. Uh, yeah, I mean...
你觉得他会送有毒的
You think he would send poisoned
甜甜圈到他孙子孙女家吗
doughnuts to the house of his grandchildren?
我确定这些甜甜圈十有八九是没毒的
No, I'm like 98% sure those are not poisoned.
好吧 这些都无关紧要 所以...
Okay. These are irrelevant, so...
不不不
Oh, no. No, no, no.
这些... 这些甜甜圈至关重要
These... these are relevant doughnuts.
我们要合作吗
So do we wanna?
各位 你们愿意吗
Guys? You wanna?
我现在立马打电话
I'll make the call right now.
我们今晚就说 一切都结束了 我们接管公司
We'll say it tonight. It's over. We're in.
新时代开启
New dawn.
老康 别再盯着那些该死的甜甜圈了 伙计
Con, stop looking at the fucking doughnuts, man.
专心点 好吗
Okay. Focus.
我退出
I'm out.
好吧 你不重要
Well, fine. You're irrelevant.
-去你妈的  -快走
- Hey, fuck you. - Go on. Go.
-不 别这样  -不需要你了
- No. Come on. - You're not wanted.
-拜托 别这样  -走走走
- Come on. No. - Go, go, go, go, go.
-没错 不需要你了  -是因为...  -这里不需要你了
- Yeah, you're not wanted. - Because... - You're not wanted.
-你要知道... 要知道...  -不 这里不需要你了
- So you know... you know... - No. You're not wanted.
-我好爱这个画面  -不需要你了
- I love this. - You're not wanted.
好像他这辈子没听够这句话一样
Like he hasn't heard that enough in his life.
-罗曼  -哥们 什么事
- Roman. - Yeah, howdy. What's up?
我们这么做吧
Let's do this.
不了吧
Uh, pass.
不了 为什么
Pass? Why?
-很多原因  -比方说
- A number of reasons. - Like what?
你觉得我赢不了吗
You... you think I can't win?
伙计 我们联手一定能赢
Dude, we will win this together.
我们绝逼会赢 拜托 伙计
We'll fucking win. I mean, come on, man.
帮我对你没什么坏处
What...what I eat don't make you shit.
这足够我们所有人分的了
There's enough for us all.
就像我说过的 我站爸那边
Uh, like I said, I'm with dad.
一直都是 我一直都站他那边
I have been. I always have been.
-跟你说过了  -你是个大蠢货
- Told you. - You're a fucking moron.
-小西 别管他们...  -我站爸那边
- Shiv, forget them... - I'm with dad.
为什么
Why?
-什么为什么 我不需要告诉你
-- Why? I don't need to tell you.
不 你得告诉我 是因为这堆烂甜甜圈吗
Yes, you fucking do. Is it the goddamn donuts?
你是被这堆烂甜甜圈给唬住了吗
Have you been spooked by fucking doughnuts?
太可悲了 小西 到底为什么
That's pathetic, Shiv. Why?
你欠我一个解释
You owe me an explanation.
没错 因为你总是
Oh, yeah, 'cause you've always
很注意让我知晓所有的信息
been very careful to keep me fully informed.
什么意思 你... 你不相信我吗
What is it? You... you don't believe me?
你肯定是信我的吧
Obviously, you believe me.
所以你就是宁愿做错事 也不要做对的事吗
So you're literally doing the wrong thing over the right thing.
-你打算这么做吗  -我看得出来你很生气
- That's what you're doing? - I can see that you're angry,
但请别把你的失望撒在我身上 好吗
but please don't project your disappointment on to me, okay?
有时候 我们有机会成就不凡
There are times to be someone.
-现在就是乘胜追击的时刻  -好吧
- It's high tide. - Okay.
-现在就是  -好吧 我要走了
- It's high tide. - Right. I ought to go.
这... 你这是胆小还是贪得无厌 我很好奇
I mean, I... i... is it cowardice or avarice? I'm intrigued.
是因为你没能接管公司吗
It's because you don't take over. Is that it?
那你走着瞧吧 小西
Well, good luck with sleeping on that, Shiv.
操你大爷 伪君子
Fuck you, plastic Jesus.
你他妈个骚屄
You're a fucking twat.
我是你唯一想要争取的人
I was the only one you wanted.
对吗 我是唯一重要的人
Yeah? I was the only one who mattered.
没错 只因为你是女的
Yeah. Only 'cause you're the girl.
女的可以投两票 你不知道吗
Girls count double now, didn't you know?
我知道 我他妈当然知道
Oh, yeah. No, I know. I fucking know.
你有价值只是因为你有奶子
It's only your teats that give you any value.
知道了吧 只是因为你有奶子
So, you know, it's only your teats.
你大错特错了
You're calling it wrong.
你辜负了那些受害者
And you're fucking over the victims.
你还会在年度股东大会上害了公司
And you're fucking the company at the AGM.
因而影响公司重新开始 还有...
And therefore renewal at the company and...
还有这个国家 或许还有整个地球
and the country and probably the planet.
-所以干得漂亮 蠢货  -我只是不想毁了爸
- So well done, dipshit. - I just don't wanna destroy dad.
我是全国瞩目的人物 弑父是不对的
I'm a national figure. It's not right to kill one's father.
-没错 你是个混蛋  -历史为鉴
- Yeah, you're a prick. - History teaches us that.
-你是个全国瞩目的大混蛋  -是啊
- You're a national fucking prick. - Yeah.
拯救地球吧 肯
Save the planet, Ken.
你也是个混蛋 晚安
You're a fucking prick. Goodnight.
-谢谢你亲自告诉我  -晚安 你个狗日的混蛋
- Oh, thanks for telling me in person - Goodnight, you fucking prick.
-蠢货  -而不是开个记者会骂我
- Idiot. - instead of calling a press conference.
-干嘛  -那些...
- What? - Those...
"另外尚未确定的是
"What's also unclear is what's
全美最大的家族经营的媒体帝国
next for the largest family-run media empire"
接下来会怎样
"In the United States."
一直以来 众人都认为
"It's long been believed
洛根·罗伊会把公司留给家里的某个人
that Logan Roy wanted to keep it in the family"
深陷丑闻的洛根·罗伊是否真的气数已尽
当他决定退位 把公司掌权交给..."
"When he decides to step aside, passing the reins of his..."
深陷丑闻的洛根·罗伊是否真的气数已尽
我想我得回城了
I think I need to get back to the city.
大家需要看到家族团聚
People need to see a little family unity.
当然了
Of course.
你确定手上有可以阻止他的东西吧
And you do have things you could say, no, to stop him?
知道吗 伤敌一千自损八百
You drop some bombs, you get burned too, you know?
-是小西吗  -是罗曼
- Shiv? - Roman.
喂 罗慕路斯
Hey, Romulus.
喂 老爸
Hey, Pop.
你找到她了吗
You got her?
谁 那个关键人吗
Who? The one who matters?
找到了 我和她在一起
Yeah, I'm with her.
她也在场吗 她动摇了吗
Was she there? Was she wobbly?
不不不 她在尝试让肯改变主意
No. No. Uh, she was trying to get to Ken to push him off course.
对 她没有音讯是因为一直在试着劝退他
Yeah, she was dark 'cause she was all in on trying to get to him.
试着劝导他 比如烧掉文件之类的
Trying to talk him around to like burn the papers.
但她没法改变他的想法
But she couldn't change his mind,
因为他已经疯了
'cause he's gone bananas.
她可靠吗
Is she solid?
是的 是的 她很可靠
Oh, yeah. Yeah, she's solid.
好的 好的 谢谢 小兔崽子
Okay. Okay. Thank you, Tumbledown.
我要离开这个鬼地方
I'm getting out of this shithole.
我们应该在一起
We should be together.
外公 这... 这不是别人推荐给我的那位律师
So, uh, Gramps, this... this isn't the lawyer I was recommended.
皮尤人不错
Pugh's a good man.
他正在帮我整理我的房产
He's helping me set my estate in order.
-各位好  -你好
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
刚才在等两倍浓缩咖啡
Just getting a double black eye.
费了吃奶的劲用强滤纸冲了杯咖啡
Strong filter with a double espresso shot.
就差没操作查尔斯·巴贝奇的差分机了[机械史上最复杂的操作]
Might as well fire up Charles Babbage's Difference Engine.
好吧[右] 真不错
All right. Nice.
-美国总是对的[右派]  -从不左倾
- America is always right. - Never left.
我想你一定会喜欢皮尤的 他是个永不妥协的人
I think you're gonna like Pugh. He's incredibly intransigent.
这样啊 那就好
Right. Good. Good. Yeah.
好了
Okay.
我可以... 你介意我...
Uh, can I... do you mind if I just...
你或许有... 你有按什么规律放吗
you probably have a... do you have a system?
-没有 就这样 放这儿就好  -好的
- No, this is it. Right here is good. - Okay.
放在首位的
So, priority one,
是你的利益和满意的结果
your wellbeing and the satisfactory outcome.
好的 耶耶耶
Good. Okay. Yes, yes, yes.
第二位的是揭露资本主义的结构性矛盾
Priority two, expose the structural contradictions of capitalism
具体表现在美国公司的架构中
as reified in the architecture of corporate America.
好的 也可以
Good. Also good.
你就是我们的小楔子 格雷格
You're our little wedge, Greg.
一个利于我们撬开引擎盖
A nice little wedge to open
对韦斯达内部一探究竟的小楔子
up the hood and have a poke around in at Waystar.
好吧 我... 我想是吧
Okay. Good. I... I guess...
我比较关注的重点是我的处境
I'm quite focused on like my position
还有确保我本人不会被炒鱿鱼
and me in particular not getting
或是去坐牢 如果这么说不是太自私的话
fired or going to jail, if that isn't too selfish.
专注目标 格雷格 专注于目标
Eyes on the prize, Greg. Eyes on the prize.
很好 我喜欢这句话
Good. I like it. I like it.
-小西在哪辆车上  -黑色的那辆
- Which one is Shiv? - That black one right there.
这辆吗 谢谢
This one? Thanks.
好哇
Hi.
-干得漂亮 格丽  -谢谢
- Well done, Gerri. - Thank you.
见到你真好 小宝
Good to see you, Pinky.
是啊 你回来真好 爸爸
Yeah, it's good to have you back, Dad.
要是能抱一个就好了
A hug would have been nice.
谢谢你送来的甜甜圈
Uh, thanks for the doughnuts.
我觉得他们已经透过窗户拍够我的照片了 所以...
You know, and I think they got enough shots of me through the window, so...
不不不 不是为了照片 就是想和你抱一下
No, no, no. Not shots. For the hug.
好吧 当然了 你"最喜欢"抱抱了
Oh, yeah. Sure. Captain Cuddles.
我打算在股东大会前让你进公司
So I wanna get you in before the shareholder meet.
高管 总裁
High level. President.
这是什么意思
What does it mean?
你想它是什么意思就是什么意思
It means whatever you want it to mean.
好吧 所以是补偿吗
Okay. So, madeup?
是想有个可靠的人位居高位
Someone at the top with credibility.
一个吉祥物吗
A mascot?
做我的耳目 小西
My eyes and ears, Shiv.
在这场风暴中 有个人要时刻处于核心
At the heart of everything through this shitstorm,
身穿全套生化防护服
but wearing a full chemical and
她的名字叫格丽·吉尔曼
biological suit going by the name of Gerri Kellman.
-来了 肯  -我的重型步兵们
- Hey, Ken. - Heavy infantry.
-欢迎  -谢谢
- Welcome. - Thank you.
赢下这件案子 想想这将为世界带来什么
Winning this case, what this is gonna do for the world.